zingpopculture.com.au 2019-03-28

# Privacy Policy - ZiNG Pop Culture

**Electronics Boutique Australia Pty Ltd. ABN 50 077 681 442** takes your concerns about the collection and use of your personal information seriously. We collect personal information from users of our Websites in the regular course of doing business. 

This notice describes our Privacy Policy, as per the requirements contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Privacy Act 1993 (NZ) (“the Acts”), and the included Australian Privacy Principles and Information Privacy Principles respectively. By visiting zingpopculture.com.au, signing up to the EB World program, or accessing the EB World smartphone app, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy sets out the type of personal information we collect from you and how we collect, hold, disclose and use that information. 

Our Privacy Policy may be revised at any time without notice to you. This Privacy Policy represents the latest version of the Zing Pop Culture Privacy Policy. 

In this document, "Zing Pop Culture" means Electronics Boutique Australia Pty Ltd, and covers EB Games and Zing Pop Culture retail stores, the zingpopculture.com.au websites, the EB World loyalty program, and the EB World smartphone app, as is relevant.

In this document, the word "computer" means any device used to connect to zingpopculture.com.au, including, but not limited to, PC’s, laptops, tablets and mobile phones.

In this document, “Websites” means the zingpopculture.com.au Websites and the EB World smartphone app, as is relevant. 

In this document, “devices” means a phone, laptop, computer or any other device that may be used to interact with our Websites, products and services. 

In this document, “users” includes customers of Zing Pop Culture and any individual who interacts with our Websites. 

## Kinds of Information Collected

Zing Pop Culture may collect, hold, disclose or use your personal information for the purpose of providing selected services to you and to ensure that you receive the best possible service. As an example, and without limiting the types of personal information we collect, we may collect your name, address, email, telephone number and accounting information such as your bank account details and credit card details including credit card number, credit card type and expiry date. 

We also collect non-personal information. Non-personal information does not identify you as an individual. For example, when you visit our Websites we may collect your Internet Protocol address, the type and version of browser you are using or the referring URL; or we may collect and summarise user information in a non-personal, aggregate format for statistical and research purposes.

Return to Top

## Personal Information: What is it?

When used in this document, "personal information" has the meaning given to it in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). It is any information that can be used to personally identify you. This may include, but isn't limited to, your name, gender, date of birth, address and contact details (including phone numbers and email addresses). If the information we collect personally identifies you, or you are reasonably identifiable from it, the information will be considered personal information.

Return to Top

## How We Collect Your Personal Information

Our Privacy Policy applies to personal information we collect during the normal operation of our business. We may collect your personal information from you when you: 

  * visit and/or transact at an Zing Pop Culture or Zing Pop Culture retail store or outlet;
  * visit and/or interact with our web presences at zingpopculture.com.au;
  * sign up to or access the EB World loyalty program;
  * access the EB World smartphone app;
  * respond to surveys;
  * enter competitions;
  * attend events hosted by Zing Pop Culture, including but not limited to EB Expo;
  * interact with our social media presences, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter and Instagram; and/or,
  * contact our Customer Service team.

We may also collect your personal information from any person authorised to provide your information or from external sources in circumstances your information is publicly and readily available. 

If we ask you for personal information for a secondary reason, like the running of competitions or games of skill, we will either ask you directly for your consent or provide you with an opportunity to decline your consent.

We may ask you to give your consent, such as by checking a box to indicate your consent to receive marketing communications, or by providing your signature to indicate your acceptance of the use and disclosure terms presented on an application form. Other times, we may obtain your consent implicitly when we can reasonably conclude that you’ve given consent by an action you have taken or an action you have decided not to take. Generally, this occurs where the purpose for use of your personal information would be reasonably apparent to you.

We will not collect personal information by unlawful means or means that are unfair or intrude on you to an unreasonable extent. 

Through use of our Websites, we may automatically record details including your internet address, domain name and the date and time of your visit to our Websites (including the web pages viewed), your browser and operating system and whether you are accessing our Websites across multiple devices or sessions. We may collect information about interactions with our Websites by you from different devices or via different sessions. We may also use cookies that allow us to track websites browsed by you. Please see heading “Automatic Collection of Information & Cookies” below for further information about the use of cookies.

Zing Pop Culture may also track your usage of our Websites via Google Analytics. You will be assigned a unique user identification (“User ID”) that allows us to track your use of our Websites from different devices and over multiple sessions. We will connect this unique User ID with your EB World loyalty account information, though we may still obtain information about your use of Websites even if you are not logged in. We may also use the Google Analytics feature to connect together all of your visits to our Websites. This will assist us in determining how you interact with our content over an extended period of time and your product preferences. 

The information collected via Google Analytics about you may include, but is not limited to, the pages you view on our Websites; the products you view on our Websites; the length of time you spend interacting with our Websites and the devices used to interact with our Websites. 

By using our Websites, you give your consent for Zing Pop Culture to track your usage of our Websites and to connect your visits to our Websites across multiple devices. We will not track your usage of any other websites. We will not upload any data that will allow Google to personally identify you or data that permanently identifies a particular device. If you would like to opt out of this feature, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject heading "Opt Out Google Analytics”. We will try to respond within 14 working days from receipt of your request.

Return to Top

## How to Change or Withdraw Your Consent

When you choose to provide us with your personal information, you consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information as stated in this Privacy Policy, and as allowed by the Acts. 

You may notify us at any time that you wish to withdraw or change your consent to our use and disclosure of your information. We will accommodate your request following receipt of such notice, subject to legal and contractual restrictions related to your transactions.

If you have signed up to our EB World loyalty program you can adjust your preferences for all communications and other contact options at any time via your online EB World profile, or by contacting our Customer Service team. We also provide an ‘Unsubscribe’ link in all marketing mailings, and the option to reply ‘STOP’ to all SMS marketing material, as required by the Spam Act 2003 (Cth).

You may request to have your EB World account deactivated, and to receive no further communications in relation to your EB World account. Deactivation of an account may not result in all related personal information being deleted, as required by legal and/or operational requirements, and allowed by applicable laws.

Return to Top

## Information That We Collect About Users

We may collect the following types of personal information:

  * name;
  * email address;
  * telephone number;
  * age or birth date;
  * mailing or street address;
  * details of the products and services you have purchased from us, together with any additional information necessary to deliver those products and services and to respond to your enquiries;
  * details of the interactions between your devices and our Websites; 
  * any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly through our Websites or indirectly through use of our Websites or online presence through our staff or otherwise; and
  * information you provide to us through contact with our Customer Service team or staff during store visits.

We receive and store any information you enter on our Websites or that you give us in any other way. You may need to provide us with personal information to take advantage of some of our features for website users. You can choose not to provide certain information, but this may limit or prevent us from providing you with the product, service or information that you requested.

We ask for your age to determine what promotions we send. We limit some promotional offers and product availability to users of a certain age or older, as required by Australian and New Zealand video game ratings regulations.

We occasionally run our own email surveys and we ask visitors for contact, demographic and technical information.

Return to Top

## Automatic Collection of Information & Cookies

Through interaction with our Websites, we will receive and store information that you provide or that is generated by your actions. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," which are placed on your computer (explained in more detail below). It lets us personalise your experience at our Websites, tailoring the content to your interests. A number of companies offer browsers or utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously, but if you use these browsers or utilities, it may limit your ability to use the Websites features we offer.

The information we receive or can determine from your interaction with our Websites includes your Internet (IP) address; login and password information to our Websites and/or your EB World account; email address; web browser type and version; operating system and computer platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other users; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Websites, including date and time; traffic data; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and/or areas of our Websites you visited. We also may log the length of time of your visit and the number of times you visit and purchase from us. We assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits.

If you do not want to collect cookies to be used to collect your personal information, you may disable cookies through your browser. However, if you do disable cookies, you may not be able to interact with our Websites or take advantage of the improved functionality that cookies enable. 

Return to Top

## Information Zing Pop Culture Collects Directly from You

### In-Store Purchases

When you purchase a product or service from Zing Pop Culture, you may need to provide us with contact and payment information (such as credit or debit card information) so that we can process your request or complete your transaction. We also may need contact information to provide delivery services, product service, and warranty coverage. If we want to use your information to send you promotional information, we will ask for your express consent.

### Trading

For any transaction that includes a Trade of software, hardware or accessories, we are required by law to witness a government-issued photo ID to prove your identity, and to record personal information such as your name, address, and your ID reference number.

### Returns and Exchanges

In connection with any returns, refunds or exchanges, we may ask for personal information such as your name, address, and telephone number for the purposes of detecting and preventing fraud. You also may be asked to produce photo identification for verification purposes. This process does not affect your statutory rights.

### Purchase Follow-Up and Surveys

Following a purchase, we may send you a follow-up communication either thanking you for your business or inquiring as to whether you are satisfied with your new product. We may use contact information collected in-store, online, or via our call centres to conduct occasional surveys and other user research. These surveys are entirely voluntary.

### Our Websites

You can browse our Websites anonymously. However, to order products and services from our Websites, or to use special features or functions of our Websites, you may be asked to provide personal information, such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, or credit or debit card information. We use this information to create your account, contact and correspond with you about your order, respond to your inquiries, and monitor functions or features of our Websites that you may use.

### Social Media

Information that you have provided via social media pages, such as providing your name or contact details via the Zing Pop Culture Facebook, Twitter or Instagram presences, may be used to contact you regarding issues or complaints registered via our social channels or other social media sites that we use.

### Customer Reviews and Posted Content

We may provide you with the ability to rate or review products or services we sell, or otherwise post content on our Websites. Any comments or reviews that you provide are accessible to all visitors to our Websites, so you should use discretion when posting information and you should not post personal information. Zing Pop Culture has no responsibility if you do post personal information. Subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Policy relating to your personal information, you grant a perpetual worldwide non-exclusive license to Zing Pop Culture to copy, use and/or display any content that you post publically on any of our websites or services.

### Loyalty Program

Zing Pop Culture may offer you the opportunity to sign up to the EB World customer loyalty program. If you decide to do so, we will collect your personal information, including but not limited to your name and email address. By signing up to the EB World loyalty program you are providing consent for us to communicate with you via email, SMS or in-app notifications. You may rescind your consent for these communications at any time by using the ‘Unsubscribe’ link provided in the footer of every marketing email sent, by replying ‘STOP’ to any marketing SMS we send you, by updating your Communications Preferences in your EB World Online Profile, or by contacting our Customer Service team.

We may also collect data from you via Google Analytics through the “User ID feature” to identify your different devices and determine interactions between your devices and our Websites, products and services. The information collected may include, but is not limited to, technical information about your devices, your browsing activity and information concerning interactions between your devices and our Websites. Any information collected via the “User ID feature” will be connected with your EB World customer loyalty program information, including but not limited to your name and email address. You may opt-out from using the “User ID feature” by contacting our Customer Service team. 

### Smartphone App

Zing Pop Culture may make available the option to access offers and services provided via a smartphone app. To access such an app you may be required to sign up to the EB World loyalty program, and provide us with personal information including but not limited to your name and email address.

Your activity within the smartphone app and connected systems, including Zing Pop Culture websites, may be stored for the purposes of software development and maintenance; marketing research; managing the provision of offers and services provided via the smartphone app; and other purposes allowed by the Acts. While parts of this data may be stored in anonymous form, personally identifiable information may also be stored.

In order to provide certain services to the EB World smartphone app, your device’s unique identifier, hardware model, operating system version, and other technical detail may be collected. In order to use certain functions on the smartphone app, you may choose to give the app access to your Photos on your device; your Photos are not collected by Zing Pop Culture or transmitted from your device, they are used exclusively within the app on the device itself.

If you choose to nominate a Nickname in your EB World profile, your Nickname may be made visible to other users of the EB World program and/or the general public. We will never use your real name, only the Nickname you have provided for this purpose.

### Contest and Other Promotions

From time to time, we may run contests or promotions. If you participate, you may be asked for contact information as well as additional optional survey information (for example, product preferences). Personal information from contest entries will be used only to administer the contest and contact you if you win. For research and analysis purposes, we may also aggregate contest survey information in a manner that no longer identifies individual participants. All contests and promotions are subject to this Privacy Policy, applicable legal requirements, and the rules provided for each particular contest or promotion. If a contest is by a third party, it will be subject to the third party’s contest rules and policies.

### Call Centres

Zing Pop Culture operates customer support call centres to respond to your questions, concerns, or complaints regarding our products or services. When you contact our call centres, we may ask for personal information to help us respond to your inquiry or to verify your identity. For example if you have a question about the status of a recent online order, we will ask for personal information to verify that you are the account holder. We may also monitor or record your telephone discussions with our customer support representatives for training purposes and to ensure service quality.

### E-mail Communications

We provide email links on our "Contact Us" page that allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments you may have. We may receive a confirmation when you open any email that we send to you, if your computer supports such capabilities. If you send us any email, we will retain such email and your email address for response. We also may compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary or duplicate messages to you.

### Information from Other Sources

If we receive any information about you from other sources, we may add it to our account information. For example, if we receive a list of subscribers to a gaming publication, and we note that you are a subscriber, we may include that information in the account information that we store about you. We also may receive page-view information from business partners who operate their own websites or for which we provide any services, or search term and search result information from searches conducted through the Websites.

Return to Top

## Use of pseudonyms and unique identifiers

In general, you are not required to provide us with your personal information. Where reasonably practicable, you may have the option of not identifying yourself or of using a pseudonym when dealing with us. However, in some instances it may be impracticable for you to remain anonymous or use a pseudonym when using our products or services. If you choose not to produce your personal information as requested, we may not be able to provide you with some of the products or services you request. 

In some circumstances, it may be necessary for us to assign you a unique identifier to allow us to carry out our functions efficiently. For example, in accessing our EB World customer loyalty program you will be assigned a Loyalty ID number. This Loyalty ID number will also act as a connecting identifier to allow Zing Pop Culture to record the webpages visited pursuant to our Google Analytics feature. For more information on the Google Analytics feature, please see the “How We Collect Your Personal Information” section of this Privacy Policy. 

Return to Top

## How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information to customise future website browsing for you, to improve our Websites and stores, and to provide you with information, promotions, offers and services, both instore, online and via our smartphone app. We will only ever use your personal information for the purpose it was obtained unless you consent to its use for another purpose or an exception applies under the Acts. 

Personal and anonymous demographic information gathered across all channels is used to learn more about users who visit our site.

The primary reasons we collect personal information from you are:

  * To complete a sales transaction with you;
  * To place pre-orders on your behalf;
  * To fulfil your requests for products, services or information;
  * To limit the possibility of fraud or error when we process your transactions, refunds and/or exchanges;
  * To administer rebates; and/or,
  * To conduct contests, promotions or surveys.

We also use your personal information for other, secondary reasons, including:

  * Customer service;
  * As part of extended service agreements;
  * To determine instances of fraud, particularly in relation to credit card use; 
  * To administer a loyalty program, including but not limited to analysing your purchases and preferences to better understand your product and service needs;
  * To tailor our online content or in-store offerings based on your preferences;
  * To measure and improve the effectiveness of our Websites or our marketing endeavours;
  * If you ask us, to offer and promote additional products and services we offer;
  * For other purposes as described in this Privacy Policy;
  * As otherwise provided or required by the Acts. 

Return to Top

## Sharing of Information

Zing Pop Culture does not sell or rent our users’ personal information to any other party. Zing Pop Culture may share personal information gathered on our Websites with Zing Pop Culture retail stores (and vice versa) and amongst our corporate parents (Gamestop), subsidiaries, affiliates or divisions for internal business purposes in accordance with the Acts. If Zing Pop Culture shares your information within its corporate family, we will ensure that your information continues to be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy and your expressed choices. Also, in the normal course of business, we may share some of your personal information with third parties acting on our behalf or as permitted or required by law. If a third party acting on our behalf has different policies than Zing Pop Culture relating to privacy, then the Websites pages through which such information is collected from you will state or provide a link to such policies.

### Disclosure of Your Personal Information

We may disclose your personal information including any unique identifiers: 

  * to our corporate parents (Gamestop), subsidiaries, affiliates or divisions to facilitate the operation of our business; 
  * to our contractors, agents or service providers for the purpose of providing you with products or services and to facilitate the operation of our business; 
  * to third parties with whom we are affiliated for the purpose of those third parties providing you with information about their services and promotions; 
  * as required or authorised by law;
  * where your information is publicly available;
  * where your information has been de-identified in a form or for statistical or research purposes; 
  * to any person with your consent;
  * where disclosure is necessary to prevent or lessen a serious threat such as public health or safety; 
  * to government or regulatory bodies when necessary; 
  * in connection with a sale of any business associated with our corporate parents, subsidiaries, affiliates or divisions;
  * to our professional advisors when required. 

If we are required by law to release information about you, we must cooperate fully. We may also disclose your information in order to investigate, halt, or take action regarding illegal activities. 

### Disclosure to Third Parties 

Zing Pop Culture may use third parties to manage one of more aspects of our business operations, including the processing or handling of personal information. 

Where your personal information is disclosed to a third party, we will take all reasonable steps to prevent unauthorised use or disclosure of your information. We may share personal information with such third parties to perform services on our behalf –

Such as:

  * email communications
  * customer lists management
  * data analysis
  * fulfilling online orders
  * processing non-cash payments via financial institutions for payment processing
  * sending marketing communications
  * servicing products
  * conducting research surveys
  * verifying and validating information that you have provided to us
  * delivering products
  * information systems maintenance
  * providing customer support services

When we do use an outside company, these companies are provided with access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but we use contractual and other appropriate means to ensure that your personal information is used in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure of Your Personal Information Overseas 

We may disclose personal information to overseas recipients amongst our corporate parents (Gamestop), subsidiaries, affiliates or divisions for internal business, who are located in both Australia and New Zealand. As a result, your personal information may be accessible to law enforcement and regulatory authorities in accordance with the laws of these jurisdictions.

Your personal information may also be accessible to our contractors, agents or service providers located in Australia and New Zealand. We will not transfer your personal information to any other overseas countries unless compelled by law or with your consent. 

You agree to cross-border transfers of your personal information as per this Privacy Policy. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that our contractors, agents or service providers located overseas do not breach your privacy. 

### Promotional Offers May be Sent to You

We may use your personal information, such as your name, address and contact details, to provide you with promotional offers or marketing information. We may send you offers on behalf of our company or other businesses we are working with if we believe that you may be interested in receiving these offers. If you do not want to receive such emails in the future, you can notify us by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link attached to each email, or by contacting our Customer Service team.

### Product Safety Recalls

In the event we receive notice from a manufacturer or supplier of a product safety recall, we may provide your contact information, limited to name, address, telephone number, and/or email address to the manufacturer so that they may notify you of the recall and supply details of any replacement or repair programs. This transfer of your contact information will occur only for recalls that may impact your personal safety or impair the functionality of the product you purchased from us.

### Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets of Zing Pop Culture

Any information we have about you may be transferred or disclosed to a purchaser or prospective purchaser in the event of a sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that the transferee uses your information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Legal Disclosure

Zing Pop Culture may disclose your information as permitted or required by law. For example, we may be compelled to release information by a court of law or other person or entity with jurisdiction to compel production of such information. If we have reasonable grounds to believe information could be useful in the investigation of improper or unlawful activity, we may disclose information to law enforcement agencies or other appropriate investigative bodies.

Return to Top

## How does Zing Pop Culture Protect Your Information?

Zing Pop Culture takes appropriate steps to protect your personal information. However, we acknowledge that the Internet is not a secure environment, and any information you send to us via that method is sent at your own risk. We maintain appropriate safeguards and current security standards to protect your personal information, whether recorded on paper or captured electronically, against unauthorised access, disclosure, or misuse. For example, electronic records are stored in secure, limited-access servers; electronic data is stored behind secured encryption access; we use technological tools like firewalls and strong passwords; and we ensure our employees are trained on the importance of maintaining the security and confidentiality of personal information. Although we cannot take responsibility for any theft, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, loss, alteration or destruction of data by a third party, we take reasonable security measures to safeguard against the loss, destruction, use, modification or disclosure of, or unauthorised access to, any personal information you have given us. Zing Pop Culture also has taken precautions to prevent the fraudulent use of your information on our Websites. Zing Pop Culture has adopted industry standard authentication procedures, as discussed below, to increase your protection while shopping with us online. This includes, but is not limited to, contacting our third party providers for payment processing, fraud detection; card and merchant management and electronic bill presentment and payment. Third party providers located in Australia and New Zealand may take actions to determine the validity of your credit card and to detect any fraud issues prior to completion of an online purchase. 

Our third party credit card processor also may take actions to determine the validity of your credit card. 

### SSL Technology

Our Websites use encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL"), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address, and credit card number.

### Choosing a Password

When you create an online account on our Websites, you will be prompted to select a personal password. To maximise your level of protection, you should choose a strong personal password, which means that you should use at least 6 characters including a combination of both letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and any account information. Zing Pop Culture will never send an unsolicited communication asking you for your password or requesting that you update your account credentials.

Return to Top

## Accessing and Verifying Your Personal Information

You are legally entitled to know what personal information an organisation holds about you and how that information is processed. If you would like to know what information we currently hold about you, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject heading "Information Access". Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, and provided we can authenticate your identity, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information within 14 working days from receipt of your request, and will be entitled to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it updated or corrected as appropriate. We do not generally charge for providing such access but may do so in certain circumstances. You also may ask us to change your preferences regarding how we use or disclose your information, or let us know that you do not wish to receive any further communication from us.

If you created an account on one of our Websites, you can access and change your online account profile yourself. You can also ask to review any of the information that we have retained, how we have used it, and to whom we have disclosed it at any time by contacting us as indicated below under the heading "Contacting Zing Pop Culture".

Return to Top

## Correcting Your Personal Information

If you ask us to correct personal information that we hold about you, or if we are satisfied that the personal information we hold is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, we will take reasonable steps to correct that information to ensure that, having regard to the purpose for which it is held, the information is accurate, up-to-date, complete, relevant and not misleading. If you would like your information corrected, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with the subject heading "Information Correction”. We will try to respond within 14 working days from receipt of your request. 

If we correct personal information about you, and we have previously disclosed that information to another agency or organisation that is subject to the Acts, you may ask us to notify that other entity. If so, we will take reasonable steps to do so, unless this would be impracticable or unlawful.

Return to Top

## When is Your Information Removed?

We keep your information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes and to meet any legal requirements. We have retention standards that meet these parameters. We destroy your information when it is no longer needed, or we remove your personally identifiable information to render it anonymous.

Return to Top

## We May Change These Terms

Whether or not you have viewed our terms and conditions of use of this Websites, or this Privacy Policy, and whether or not you have chosen to not receive notices from us, those terms and notices will still govern your use of our Websites. We may update or change our terms of use and this Privacy Policy at any time, as we determine is appropriate. It is your responsibility to review them for changes.

Return to Top

## Contacting Zing Pop Culture

Zing Pop Culture is responsible for all personal information under its control. Our Privacy Compliance Manager is accountable for Zing Pop Culture compliance with the principles described here. If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the privacy practices of our organisation please contact us at the following:

Email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

You may contact our Privacy Compliance Manager or a member of the senior management team:

Privacy Compliance Manager  
Corporate Information  
Electronics Boutique Australia Pty Ltd.  
ABN 50 077 681 442  
25 Backhouse Place  
Trade Coast Central  
Eagle Farm, QLD 4009 Australia  
Telephone: + 61 73860 7777  
Facsimile: + 61 73860 7710 

If you have made a complaint regarding your privacy and are unsatisfied with our response, you may wish to direct your complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commission at <http://www.oaic.gov.au/>, via phone on 1300 363 992 or in writing to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner, GPO Box 5218, Sydney NSW 2001. 

If you reside in New Zealand, you may wish to direct your compliant to the office of the Privacy Commissioner via email on [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)nz, via phone on 0800 803 909 or in writing to the Office of the Privacy Commissioner, PO Box 10 094, The Terrace, Wellington 6143. 

View our Terms and Conditions of Use

Return to Top
